♪ In the not-too-
distant future
♪ Way down in Deep 13
♪ The evil Dr. Forrester
♪ Was hatching a nasty scheme
♪ He hired a temp
by the name of Mike
♪ Just a regular Joe
he didn't like
♪ His experiment needed
a good test case
♪ So he conked him
on the noggin
♪ And he shot him into space
Get me down!
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst I can find
♪ La-la-la
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all
♪ -Ooh-ooh-ooh
-And I'll monitor his mind
♪ La-la-la
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control
♪ -Ooh-ooh-ooh
-Where the movies begin or end
♪ La-la-la
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity
♪ With the help
of his robot friends
♪ Robot Roll Call:
♪ -Cambot!
-Show yourself!
♪ -Gypsy!
-I'm not ready!
♪ -Tom Servo!
-Hello there.
♪ -Crow!
-That's one "O."
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♪ -Ooh-ooh-ooh
-And other science facts
♪ La-la-la
♪ Just repeat to yourself,
"It's just a show,
♪ I should really just relax.
Did I tell you my mother's here?
♪ Fo r Mystery Science Theater
30 0 0!
Hello everyone and welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
And if I could say
in all sincerity
that it really is
a satellite of love this week
as I'm holding my annual auction
to help the really good cause!
Wait, wait, wait.
What's it for?
It's for the really,
uh, sad kids with hurt puppies.
Okay.
[ Clears throat ]
Christy, if you please,
how much am I bid for this
first item: a penny.
Huh.
A penny. This classic, durable
handcrafted penny.
I'll start the bidding
at 85 dollars.
[ Clears throat ]
No? Who'll give me a dime?
A penny?
Uh, let's move on.
Um, Christy, uh,
get the nickel.
Okay. Sure.
-The nickel.
-Our staff combed the globe
looking for the best,
cost-no-object nickel,
and this is it!
What am I bid for this nickel?
[ Clears throat
Come on!
-The hungry rainforest...
-You gonna bid on this one?
depends on--
[ Sighs ]
Well, let's move on.
[ Chuckles ] Uh, the...
Oh, right. Okay.
...dollar.
Dollar. Hey.
-A dollar.
-Oh, now. Ooh.
I'll give you 60 cents for that,
I guess.
Um, 75.
Sold!
Okay, let's tally up
the grand total, if you could?
-That's a pretty good deal.
-Christy...
Uh, let's see, it was
$1.06 for the items,
uh, 12 bucks for the material
to make the stands.
Uh, the tux was 300 bucks, okay.
Well, we lost only 312 dollars
and 31 cents!
Well, hey!
And next year we'll lose
even more! [ Laughs ]
Yes. Ah, thank you, everyone.
Thank you, you cheap,
heartless bastards.
Wow.
We'll be right back after I talk
to Bob Geldof here. Crow!
[ Humming ]
Crow, I-- I think
you should admit
that your little
auction fundraiser
was nothing
but a fraudulent attempt
to line your own pockets
with some easy cash.
Uh-huh.
You know, uh, I hate to ask,
what are you doing now?
Uh, well, the angle
of the sun is just right,
so I, uh, I thought
I'd burn this ant I found
while I was organizing
my oily rags.
Oh, what next?
An ant? Crow, doesn't that seem
pointless and cruel?
Like there's gonna be some kind
of divine retribution.
[ Laughs ]
-Well, maybe--
-Bingo!
[ Laughs ]
-This is the saddest thing--
-Ah!
Whoa!
My oily rags!
Oh!
[ Blows on flames ]
Hi, guys. Some bad news,
although I'm sure
you could see it coming
just as well as I could.
I finally had to
put Mom in a home.
Clayton!
She'd really been
slipping lately,
just off in another world.
Like last week she said,
"Clayton,
where's the coat rack?"
[ Chuckles ]
"Where's the coat rack?"
We don't even have a coat rack.
[ Laughs ]
Well, I guess we do,
but she's just--
Her mind is gone.
Clayton, you get me out
of this house right now.
Wow.
[ Alarm blares ]
Ah! Ah!
Oh!
The flames have spread
to those oily rags
on Level 12, Mike!
Cambot,
to the rocket number nine!
[ Flames roaring ]
[ Alarm blaring ]
Uh-- uh, prepare
to jettison the core!
We don't have a core!
We're all gonna die!
[ Crow singing ]
♪ ...my God to thee --
Thank you for those kind words,
but in the end,
this is the sort
of personal tragedy
that we must deal with
in our own way.
Clayton, I don't like it
in here.
Well, I promised her I'd visit.
Uh, it's-- it's
not a lot of fun,
but, uh, she does seem
to enjoy seeing me.
[ Choking ] Oh, hello, Mother.
It's me, Clayton.
Do you recognize me?
MRS. FORRESTER: Clayton,
you let me out of here!
Oh, I'd love to, Mother,
but I can't.
[ Struggling efforts ]
Clayton!
Well, Mike, your movie this week
is Escape 2000 .
It's... really the kind of thing
Mother would enjoy
had she still control
of her faculties.
Clayton! Clayton, I'm hungry.
Clayton!
Oh. "I'm hungry. I'm tired."
It never stops.
Death would be a blessing.
[ Alarm blaring ]
[ Sobbing ]
Oh, good-- oh, good God!
Just give me that movie sign
or we're all gonna die!
[ Mike sobbing]
It's my fault! It's my fault!
You're not going to die.
Now get in the theater!
Okay.
Cambot, activate
the sprinkler system!
Phew. Well.
Wow.
That was scary, huh?
Hey, why
is John Madden signing
Samuel Goldwyn's signature?
Samuel Goldwyn,
father of the Constitution.
[ Chuckles ]
Wow, the new
draconian HUD policies.
Hmm.
Hello?
You are ordered
to leave the Bronx.
I repeat, you are ordered
I forgot my luggage!
This area has been declared
uninhabitable
and destined for demolition.
Leave now and leave peacefully.
Okay, you convinced me!
The government guarantees
to relocate all of you
in comfortable, up-to-date
alternative accommodations.
Mm-hm.
Leave the Bronx.
Even though this is Italy,
leave the Bronx.
I repeat, you are ordered
to leave the Bronx.
You, too, Henry Silva.
This area has been declared
uninhabitable
and destined for demolition.
Therefore we suggest you...
- Leave the Bronx.
-Le ave the Bronx.
Leave peacefully.
You have nothing to fear.
The government guarantees
to relocate all of you
in comfortable...
- So leave the Bronx.
- Look, leave the Bronx.
Vote Johnson, vote Johnson!
...unauthorized occupancy.
Isolate immediately.
Hey, I had the radio on.
I didn't hear.
Am I supposed to
leave the Bronx?
...to leave the Bronx.
The area has been declared
uninhabitable
- and destined for demolition.
-Is o late are a B6.
And we have a bingo.
Hold your cards, please.
Evacuation of area M3
is now complete.
Wait a minute, right there.
Cordon off. Repeat,
cordon off area M3.
Lunch today: tater tots,
Jell-O, pigs in a blanket.
Hang on, Earl, I gotta read
this sign here.
"Leave the Bronx."
Oh, gee.
I repeat, you are ordered
to leave the Bronx.
Yeah, I gotta tell ya,
it looks like
everybody's left the Bronx, Ted.
Pretty much.
Leave now
and leave peacefully.
We gratefully acknowledge
the Reynolds Wrap corporation
for donating the costumes.
The government guarantees
to relocate all of you
in comfortable, up-to-date
alternative accommodations.
I think they're
really overselling
the New Mexico thing.
You are ordered
to leave the Bronx.
I repeat, you are ordered
Well, I suppose
I oughta leave the Bronx.
I thought it was
a suggestion.
When Habitat For Humanity
cracks down.
Hey. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, you guys.
Paco cannot leave.
You should have left earlier.
Eliminate.
Wow, the Orkin men
have snapped.
Don't!
[ Paco screams ]
Yow, that stang!
Damn it, he should
have left the Bronx.
Hmm.
Second disinfestation group
is now operational.
Hmm?
Go with group 5.
I repeat, go with group 5
to sectors H8...
If you leave the Bronx,
we'll give you Fudgsicles.
...sectors H8 and H9.
Groups 2 and 5
covering sectors H8 and...
- Ziggy Stardust.
- Yeah.
Skyboy 3 to Central.
I'm over sectors M6-0 and M6-1.
Negative readings.
Repeat: negative readings.
Oh, and leave the Bronx.
Central to Skyboy 3,
converge sector D8.
Your man was sighted
in the area of sector D8.
He got by the Manhattan squad,
and they lost him.
Make sure you don't
do the same thing.
You oughta try searching
this method.
Hold it.
I think you're gonna
like this one.
Hold it.
I've seen something.
- A building!
- Stand by.
Well, Valerie Bertinelli
hasn't left the Bronx.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Mike singing ]
♪ Working on a sex far m.
I better get over
to the Zombie Nightmare set.
Skyboy 3 to Central.
It's Trash, we've got him.
He's a sitting duck!
Woo-hoo!
We finally got that son of a...
in our sights.
Hmm, Trash sense danger.
Those squibs
were meant for me!
We have mortgage subsidies
for you if you'll just move
to New Mexico.
I'm a pretty good
judge of people
who aren't gonna
leave the Bronx,
and this guy is one of 'em.
Mm-hm.
Wow, it would be horrible to die
to the strains
of David Sanborn.
This was once
a glorious McDonald's Playland.
Oh, no, Dave's van!
- Man.
Come on, be a sitting duck
like you were before.
Eddie Money, no!
You just took down
Flying Officer Irv Peterson.
Wahoo!
[ Chuckling ]
Wow.
Wow, it's stayin' up there
a long time. Hmm.
I'd better take
a light wrap.
It's all really annoying,
'cause he was planning
on leaving the Bronx anyway.
What do you know?
It looks like most
of the buildings
have left the Bronx.
[ Crow chuckles ]
Isn't this where
they filmed Dollm an?
-[ Mike laughs ]
-I've just got a feeling.
I wouldn't know.
All units to D8.
Group nine cover
his parents' apartment.
Something about
"despairing the partridge"?
I didn't catch it...
See, this is the danger
of expanding rock videos
to full-length features.
Ah.
Readings indicate
he hasn't gone underground
and he may be headed
for his parents.
Or perhaps his Aunt Silvia.
[ Indistinct ]
How the hell should I know?
Whether Trash
shows up or not,
the parents are
to be eliminated.
The parrots are
to be eliminated?
- ...are to be eliminated.
-Cool.
Let's go.
Yes, the Bronx: gateway
to the Great Lakes.
Graffiti's rather tame.
Their uniforms have
a black, breathable
cotton panel.
Yeah.
We're here to see
the one bedroom.
[ Tom mimics heavy breathing ]
Gary, honey, how do you
keep your helmet
from fogging up?
Why are
the Mercury Seven here?
Honey, we've been
through this
a hundred times before.
We are the men
from Servicemaster.
But it's a matter
of principle.
Now, we're right to stay.
Okay, first
we'll ask them nicely
to turn down their TV.
For 28 years
and tell us
we gotta move to New Mexico!
Who the hell wants to...
They're rehearsing
a David Mamet play.
Jesus!
No. No...
I shouldn't have
seen Showgi rls
before I came up here.
Now if you wanna go,
you go.
Oh, Joe, you know
I wouldn't go without you,
but maybe...
He's married to Jo Anne Worley?
I mean, we never been there,
so do we know?
They're not throwing me out,
damn it.
I can't leave all this.
They're not throwing me out
of my own house.
Please, Joe. Do it for me.
I'm Tyne Daly.
We can't give in to those...
We were born here,
for Christ's sake.
"Bad guys",
I think he said.
Oh, okay.
Joe, I understand.
I really do.
I just don't think
it's worth the pain
or worth the misery
of living in fear.
We're here to tenderize.
WO No, Joe!
Oh!
Oh, what are we gonna do?
They're not getting
the Tom of Finland posters.
Here's what I'm gonna do.
Oh, no,
it'll make it worse!
I'll show 'em.
I'll show 'em this.
I got it at Sportmart.
-No, Joe! No!
-Hey, guys, look at this.
Oh!
Ooh, that good aluminum
on that one.
Sir, would you at least take
a Watcht ower? Ow!
Come on!
No!
Come and get me,
or I'm gonna smash
your skulls in.
Uh, sir, by now
I'm sure you've heard about
our Leave the Bronx program.
My contacts! Ooh!
[ Screams ]
Good one, big shot.
You didn't wanna
leave the Bronx.
No!
Oh, no!
No! Not my fine washables!
[ Screams ]
I-- I'm ready to live
the Southwest lifestyle.
A little taste
of the weather
-in New Mexico.
[ Screams ]
[ Crow singing ]♪ Kawasaki ,
let's the good times roll .
Ah, it's Evel Knievel's
handicap access.
[ Tom chuckling ]
I was sleepin' up here!
And I can't even have a cat
in my apartment building.
[ Tom chuckling ]
[ Tom singing ]
♪ Purple rain, purple rai n.
He's got kind of
an inconvenient parking spot.
Gotta be a cash machine
around here somewhere.
Well, it's just a good thing
he doesn't drive a bus.
[ Mike laughs ]
I gotta check
my Roquefort cheese, man.
Drip, drip.
Uh, where's the sound?
Uh, I'll do it. Yep.
[ Crow makes footstep noises ]
Okay, let's see.
[ Tom singing ]
♪ Peg, I hear you call --
No, no.
[ Tom singing ]
♪ Debbie, I hear you c --
No, no.
Satan? Satan?
Welcome
to the Honeycomb Hideout.
Hold it. Hold it!
Well, hi, Walker,
Texas Ranger.
What got into you?
The next time you don't give
the signal--
Uh, yeah, you know.
[ Chuckles ]
...I'll just have
to blow your brains out.
Yeah, Trash,
who do you think you are?
The President?
Ah!
God, don't tease Trash,
I guess.
Come on, try again.
I'm in the shower!
Now break this up.
[ Tom singing ]
♪ Mystery Dat e.
[ Tom gasps ]
Hmm.
Frankie Goes to Hollywood.
Hi.
It's the cast of Fame!
Whoa.
[ All singing ]
♪ In the Nav y.
[ Tom singing ]
♪ On e.
Keep poppin', baby.
Say it, Trash.
Still alive, huh?
Listen, honey,
I am still waiting.
Uh, no comment.
Hey, what's up?
-Just let me see.
-Sure.
Now slice it like a lime.
Ooh, wait a minute. Hey.
[ All singing ]
I really need this job.
[ Mike singing ]
♪ And I want to have --
And three, and--
Ammo.
You ask for ammo,
I bring you ammo.
I sent you out
for waxworms!
Okay, why are you getting
so excited?
Stay cool.
Man, I tell you something.
I really think you are
pretty damn good,
coming and going all the time.
Well, well, isn't that nice?
Flattery and compliments.
Prince needs a decaf,
pronto.
Oh, by the way,
next time the price
of ammunition's going up.
Hey, don't you think
you're ripping us off enough?
[ Speaks in Spanish ]
I don't get you.
[ Laughs ]
Vamos.
I feel that you deserve
Bronx gangs,
but you're holed up down here
eating out of tin cans.
Well...
Uh, I need a check signed.
...we're alive and kicking,
my friend.
Uh, there's a soda delivery
up front.
Whereas up there,
they kill us like animals.
One, two, three...
Hey, hey, what's
our FedEx number?
There's a guy out front.
Hello?
Hey, what are you guys
doing here?
[ Shouts in Spanish ]
Go paint some more hats!
[ Spits ]
Ha!
The One Minute Manager.
[ Laughs ]
Hmm.
Don't change the subject.
-Hey, look at that.
-Pigs talk a lot.
It's all bark and no bite.
- Hmm?
-Here, I brought you this.
It's the lyrics
to that Whitesnake song
- I was telling you about.
- Here.
Just in case you run out
of toilet paper.
I'll put that
on still store.
[ Chuckling ]
Ha. Get out of the Bronx,
they say.
We've got solar houses
in enchanting New Mexico
waiting for you.
[ Shouts in Spanish, laughs ]
The Italians
really embrace life.
While you're laughin',
they're wastin' innocent people.
You know what the problem
with you guys is, Dablone?
-You ran too quick.
- His name is Toblerone?
Now you're tryin'
to make a stand.
Well, the ones with guts
didn't scare so easy.
Oh, sure. Look who's talking,
Superman.
[ Laughs ]
What about my old man
and my old lady
and others like them?
Just try and move them out
of the Bronx.
Nah, you turned
chicken too soon, that's all.
If you had any brains...
you would tell them
to come here, underground.
We've got
a great food court.
Where these Disinfestors
will-- never coming.
[ Laughs ]
Ha, ha-ha-ha, ha?
Yow ha how, why did I think
this was a good idea?
New positive readings,
sector H8.
Renegade.
Uh, may I suggest a rake?
[ Chuckling ]
Ah, sector H8.
I love it here.
Oh, man, if only
there had been
enterprise zone legislation
none of this would be a problem.
This would be-- Hey!
Oh, sorry, Dad. Gee.
Yep. Ooh.
Geez, so he parked
in your space.
Come on.
All right,
I got the accordion.
[ Chuckles ]
Place is just filled
with oily rags.
It's great.
It's some of the politest,
most informative graffiti
- I've ever seen.
- Mr. Lee.
Mr. Lee.
Have you seen
a knife like this?
But wait, there's more.
[ Fighting efforts ]
[ Mocking knife slash noises ]
Ah, now, he'll flash back
to the Shaolin monastery.
Adam Sandler!
Get him!
- Get him!
- Yes!
ALL: Yes!
Oh, yeah.
Ha! Yah!
Hmm?
[ Grunts ]
Oh, George Hamilton
didn't know
when to stop tanning.
[ Tom singing ]
♪ Wash and go, Pert Plu s.
Ooh.
[ Grunts ]
Sorry, Uncle Ron.
[ Chuckling ]
A horrible fondue accident.
[ Tom coughs ]
We just wanted
to dry off the cat.
That was my favorite chair.
You shoulda
left the Bronx, Dad!
[ Gunshots ]
He took out Horshack.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Grunts ]
He's dead already.
Come on!
Dad?
Kathy Bates!
Lorenzo Lamas,
in the Gino Vannelli story.
Dinner's in the fridge,
honey.
Yet her Orlon sweater
survived.
Can I have
the overturned chair?
This, ladies and gentlemen,
will be the
New York of the future.
The most magnificent
architectural complex
ever created by man.
The Eighth Wonder of the World.
Me.
This work of genius,
ladies and gentlemen,
was conceived and promoted
by our president, Mr. Clark,
who has committed
all the company's resources
to the project.
[ Applause ]
Wow, the new stuff killed.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I invented
New York City.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
As you can all see,
it's a suspended city,
linked to the
other inhabited zones.
Will it still be
a hell of a town, sir?
A perfect, ordered,
civilized metropolis.
Get your hand off my ass.
Serviced by the most modern
technology available.
Every building will have
Selectric typewriters.
A city in which
there are no social blots.
Areas of poverty, illiteracy,
and crime...
...are built in.
...like the Bronx, will have
been totally eliminated.
It's about time.
The Bronx is a public disgrace.
Right on. It should go.
The crime rate's horrendous.
The Bronx is a plague.
It's got to be relieved.
The people from those areas
are guaranteed accommodation
and a higher standard of living
in New Mexico.
That just isn't true.
Honey, please.
Why the hell don't you admit
you're deporting
and killing them?
That you're causing accidents
and epidemics
to eliminate those people
who put up
the slightest resistance
to being thrown out
of their rightful homes?
Get her out of here.
But I'm with Parade!
Hands off me, you fascist pig!
A fascist Italian?
Come on.
This is supposed
to be a democracy.
You others, don't believe a word
they're saying! It's lies!
Get her out.
This isn't a press conference,
it's a farce!
An unadultered, filthy,
dirty farce!
Ya hear me?
And the GC Corporation sucks!
Is that true?
Do you suck?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we live in a democracy.
Mm-hm.
It's only right
to answer the questions
asked by bonafide,
professional journalists.
Sir, what's
'bonafide' mean?
Not the hysterical outbursts
of so-called crusaders.
Probably that time
of the month for her, uh...
Continue, Mr. Hoffman.
Um, I--
I was pretty much done.
Any questions?
The Bronx has been in quarantine
for two months.
When will the press
and television be allowed in?
When the killing's done.
The epidemic isn't
under control yet
and that isn't the worst danger
we want to avoid
exposing you to.
Uh, Mr. Hoffman,
exactly what danger
do you mean?
Well, the Bronx has become
a kind of no man's land,
controlled by street gangs.
As to the transfer of the,
let's say, honest residents,
what truth is there in the rumor
they're being forced out?
-Steve Higgins!
-Total nonsense.
Hey.
They have been
financially compensated
and relocated
with their full consent.
Uh, what evidence is there...
[ Mike in a mocking voice]
"Uh, what evidence is there?"
We have a great deal
of photographic documentation
showing their current
splendid residential areas
in New Mexico.
Plus affidavits
from the thousands
who've gone there.
Now, all this will
be made public
as soon as the operation
is completed.
Attention, attention,
abandon all buildings.
-Ye who enter here.
-This is the final warning.
Abandon all buildings.
The Bronx has hit an iceberg
and is sinking.
Abandon all buildings.
They are about
to be demolished.
And I'm mainly talking
to you, Steve.
Attention,
this is your final warning.
Abandon all buildings.
They are about
to be demolished.
I think they blew
their cover here.
They are about
to be demolished.
Attention.
Mm-hm?
Abandon all buildings.
What's the word
from headquarters, sir?
We now go for a response
from headquarters.
The Very Large Corporation
of America.
There he is.
Get him!
[ Chuckling ]
Um, reporter
peas and carrots.
Journalistic watermelon.
Investigative sassafras.
But that's not
really our story.
Nothing we don't
already know.
That's bull...
Oh, yeah.
See ya later.
[ Chuckles]
Another great scene.
Look, however much good we do,
there are always those
who will find some
reason or other to knock it.
When will the demolition
ceremony take place?
[ Tom mocking
high-pitched babble ]
How are you answering
the UN Human Rights commission?
It's all in the dossier
we gave to you.
President Lincoln,
you had a question.
[ Reporters murmuring ]
I can't--
Mr. Clark,
what about that issue--
What's the best way
to take care of leg cramps?
Is it really bad
to clean your toaster
with a knife?
How do I invest
in a Fannie Mae?
I told you, all the information
is in the dossier.
You didn't put these
in the dossier,
did you, though?
Ooh.
You didn't dare
include the identity
of who you put in charge
of the Bronx evacuation.
Floyd Wangler,
and we all know who--
Wind Wangler?
I told ya!
An expelled prison warden
and a killer.
Please, please if you could
keep all your rhubarbs
to a minimum.
Break it up. Make way.
Make way.
Oh, geez,
I won't build a development.
Boy, you try to be nice.
Yeah, here's your man,
Floyd Wangler,
hired killer!
-Okay, all set up.
-Okay.
Now, you wanna keep it
below this line, all right?
Hey, what's
with all the lamp cord here?
Has some Radio Shack project
gone horribly wrong?
[ Chuckling ]
No, you big dope.
It's biofeedback.
Helps with my headaches,
and then I thought
I'd get Crow set up here
so that he can relax.
Biofeedback? Ah!
What a load of crap.
It's nothing but snake oil,
my friend.
No, it sounds cool.
Come on, you losers,
didn't you see
that one 60 Minutes episode?
-No.
Well, I'm sure there was one,
and they found out
that biofeedback
is a bunch of hoo-ha.
Lame-o's.
Never mind, Mike.
Alls that matters
is if it works.
Uh, does it?
Well, it sure seems to help me.
Okay, you're set.
-Okay.
-Now...
[ Clears throat ]
Uh, just relax,
and you'll start to feel
your fingertips warm up, okay?
-Mm-hm, okay.All right.
-Just relax, okay.
Relax and now the tension will
slowly start to melt away. Okay?
[ Crow softly gasps ]
All right, great. All right.
Now relax. Good,
you're doing a good job.
[ Explosion ]
Just relax.
[ Alarm sounds ]
[ Coughs ]
Fire! We got a fire!
What the...?
What is it, Servo?
I don't know.
We got several small
spontaneous fires
bursting out
throughout the ship.
D'oh! Crow back it off a bit.
[ Explosion ]
[ Tom coughs ]
Uh, uh, uh, get Gypsy.
Go to Condition Red.
[ Alarm sounding ]
Okay.
Ah, yes. Very restorative. Ah.
[ Laughs ]
[ Saxophone music ]
[ Tom in Barry White voice ]
Oh, baby.
Yes, I just love
that charbroil flavor.
Oh, yes, uh, crispy skin.
Maybe I should go to, uh,
junior college for a while.
Okay, Trash,
let's take it again.
Remember, you're really upset,
your parents
have been fried and--
Ah, forget it.
Evacuate all buildings at once.
Are they still on that kick?
This is your final warning.
Demolition squads are about
to go into action.
I repeat: Evacuate all buildings
at once.
Demolition squads are about
to go into action.
The remaining pizza
will go on sale.
...about to go into action.
- This is your final warning.
- E ww.
I repeat,
this is your final warning.
- I wanna carry it. No!
- I wanna carry it.
Locked and loaded targets.
Comin' up.
Henry Silva,
supplied by Rent-A-Silva.
There's still
somebody inside, sir.
Oh, I'm sorry. I was off
in some daydreamy world.
What did you say was inside?
No, sir. I said
there's still somebo--
Oh, right, uh, rats?
Roaches?
Perhaps I didn't
make myself--
Oh, I see. Very clever, sir.
Right.
Proceed!
Geez, he's got
Ricky Ricardo
Tourette syndrome.
-[ Mike chuckles ]
- Whew!
Come on, move your butts!
Take over that building now!
-Run!
- Right, come on you guys.
Chauffeur is gonna
clean up this town.
That building. Dynamite it!
Or hang batteries on it
or somethin'.
Go get the wire!
You!
Lick me!
Move that truck!
I hate middle management.
Mr. Wangler, sir.
Call from Mr. Clark for you.
Fine. I'll take it now.
Good, since
he's on the phone now.
Move back.
Move back under cover.
Demolition is about to start.
All squads move back.
They're ditchin' us.
Gary saw a silverfish! Ah!
Uh... Realistic makes one
that says,
"Explode, not explode."
[ Explosion ]
Frank sneezed!
[ Crow chuckling ]
Hey, from the inside
it's not so bad.
Oh, gee.
Was today the day
we were supposed
to leave the Bronx?
[ Explosion ]
War-torn the Bronx.
Dah,
I gotta call Schneider.
[ Explosion ]
[ Trash grunts ]
Geez, I hope I can still
get my mailbox open.
[ Explosion ]
[ Trash Grunts ]
Uh, for the rent I pay
I should not have
to put up with this crap.
This is why
they don't allow hotplates.
I wish
that they would at least
put up a sign
when the elevator is out.
Oh, the Bronx is something
which I should have left.
[ Explosion, Trash screams]
Well, it was going well
till then.
[ Explosion ]
They're blowing up models
to get rid of him.
Ah, the ladder
of Damocles.
Yeah, so far
his greatest adversary
is a ladder.
[ Mike singing ]
♪ Barracud a.
Should I move or-- or no?
Or move? Hmm?
This is tension, right?
Yeah.
This caretaker job
is harder
than I thought it would be.
Geez, is it Monday?
[ Chuckles ]
Must...
get to Whitesnake tapes.
[ Metal groans ]
[ Grunts ]
This would make
a cool coffee table.
I gotta save it.
[ Explosion ]
Someone left a burrito
in the microwave!
[ Crow chuckles ]
It tossed him
into the streets of Rio Br avo.
Wow.
[ Mike chuckles ]
Listen, Wangler,
I've got the media on my back
from morning to night,
and I don't know
what to tell them anymore.
I'm paying you
damned good money.
Well, it's Italian money.
And look at the results I get.
Are you anywhere
in this car?
In five days,
the Bronx operation
...is coming up at the UN.
And I've got Jazzercise.
You know what they're calling
your methods?
Genocide.
His head's shaped
like a peanut.
The technical term
is disinfestation.
[ Tom with lisp ]
Disinfestation?
Now you pay me to take care
of the technical side.
Mm-hm.
The moral part is--
is not my sector.
The important thing is to--
to do the job cleanly.
[ Mike with lisp ]
The disinfestation?
Mr. Wangler?
In 1986, despite all
our technical know-how,
we did not succeed
in getting rid of the rats.
That's the plot
of Fievel Goes West, anyway.
Now, these people,
if you can call 'em that,
they are, uh, a race apart.
Isn't he Michele Lee?
They're what's left
of the gangs
that battled for the Bronx.
I'm not speaking
to you anymore.
You're worse than they are,
Mr. Wangler.
Allow me to correct you,
Mr. Clark.
I'm worse than anybody.
'Cept that one guy.
He was really worse.
There's gotta be
a launching pad
around here somewhere.
[ Mike singing ]
♪ Once had lov e,
and it was a gas,
soon turned out...
There's a bunch over there.
[ Muffled singing ]
They've decided to leave.
What?
[ Muffled, indistinct ]
What? I don't--?
[ Muffled ]
What do we do? Burn 'em?
Nothin'.
We must protect
this dirty box.
Aha! The cast
of any cable access program.
You know,
I actually don't mind
if they burn these guys.
[ Tom chuckling ]
Hi. Say, you guys feel
like leaving the Bronx?
Ah, Mr. Homeless People,
once again we see
there is nothing you can possess
that I cannot take away.
[ Tom chuckling ]
Come on, wake up.
No, I'm a ghost. Boo.
[ Tom chuckling ]
Is... this your indigent?
[ Gunfire, groans]
Do you know if they lived
in Manhattan,
they could have gotten rid
of the Jeffersons?
[ Gunfire ]
[ Groans ]
He had a chicken
under his coat.
Let's take the Chunnel.
[ Gunfire ]
How 'bout a little fire,
spaceman?
[ Gunfire and groans]
Quit disinfestating us.
Eww. Eww.
Eww, chunks.
[ Growls, gunshots firing ]
[ Groans ]
Understood, Skyboy 5.
Am I thinking that
or hearing that?
To all disinfestation squads,
to all disinfestation squads,
emergency alert.
He's got a toupee
under his nose.
Converge on sector R2-R.
Repeat: R2-R.
-Terror is our strength...
- Could you...?
-and he isn't even afraid of us.
-Wait. Wait.
The gangs must not be allowed
to find a leader.
Oh, um, is this--?
We've got to find this Trash
and kill him, now.
[ Train horn ]
Later,
in enchanting New Mexico.
Now, it's kind of
out of the way,
but they've got great omelets.
Down here's my bong room.
Woo.
You sure you know
where the fuse box is?
Cathy Ladman,
Private Eye.
[ Mimics Islamic
call to prayer ]
Ahn-haaalla... Oh.
Look to this slum,
graduate.
Here comes the bookmobile.
Ready.
Snipes, Bertinelli,
Escape 2000.
We're right
under LaGuardia Square.
She's got
a Bobbi Flekman voice.
Judging from the stink,
I'd say we're under
the public toilets.
Oh, that's my Chanel.
Oh, shoot, I need a jump.
You guys have cables?
Trash, you're missing
your welding class.
[ Tom imitating the score ]
Chicka chicka chicka boom
Uh, you're-- you're kinda
in my way. Blocked my, uh--
Get back there.
Uh-huh. Right.
[ Whistles ]
You, twirl around.
Hey, you.
[ Tom singing ]
Ooh, I'm driving
my life away...
- So you like it?
-We have to risk it, Jay.
What the hell for?
You think four lousy pictures
of their dirty works
gonna change things?
So far talking's done no good.
Come on.
Mandy Patinkin gets a tour
of the sewer.
[ Tom mimics the score ]
Howard Stern
in West Side Story.
Formerly Dan's
Diaper Service
now the annihilation squad.
Your DAS marching band.
[ Mouth trumpet
and drum noises ]
The Good Humor organization
in a show of force.
Under no circumstances
look to the right, men.
They've got
Rhoda Morgenstern.
Steve Dallas, terrorist.
[ Tom mimics drums ]
Ever since
the salmonella outbreak,
the Schwan's truck
needs high security.
Can we ride in the van?
I mean, there's nobody in there.
Steven Tyler, action hero.
[ Gunfire ]
[ Groans ]
We're being attacked.
Take cover!
Good luck.
Let me know what happens!
If they see us, we've had it.
Just thought
you should know that.
[ Groans ]
[ Gunfire ]
I regret nothing!
Sonia Braga looks on.
[ Gunfire, groans ]
I was unable to make them
leave the Bronx.
[ Mike mimics dying groan ]
[ Gunfire ]
Should've cut earholes
in this thing.
Hold up! Let me untie you!
Get away. Get away.
I'm rigged with a bomb.
Get away. Go on, leave me.
Seems stupid in retrospect.
Get out of here!
Get away! He's gonna blow!
Run!
Nice slide, and he's safe.
[ Gunfire, Crow giggling ]
[ Groans ]
[ Gunfire ]
D'oh. I'm shot
and then you trip me. Great.
[ Crow giggling ]
Quick, Jay. There.
There's others coming.
But if they see us,
we've had it.
[ Siren blaring ]
[ Groans ]
I am gonna take the crap
outta this picture.
[ Groans ]
You've seen me,
and I've had it.
[ Tom chuckling ]
It's a funny gag lighter.
[ Screams ]
I know it's wrong,
but he smells delicious.
[ Gunfire ]
[ Groans ]
D'oh! There was supposed
to be a mat.
You know, a year after
they restore the Bronx
it's gonna be
karate schools anyway.
Yeah.
Fred Biletnikoff!
[ Siren blaring ]
It's the S.W.A.T.
bread delivery.
[ Tom chuckling ]
Geez, look at all this
good particle board
people are throwin' away.
[ Gunfire ]
Hey, I wonder if that's
the dirty box from earlier.
Hmm.
She looks
like Shelley Duvall
after a drinking binge.
Please, ma'am,
if you go to New Mexico,
you'll have a nice view
of cacti.
Uh, you could live
in a really nice artist colony?
You-- you might
meet Joni Mitchell?
Hello?
[ Gasps ]
Freeze.
[ Gunfire, groans ]
Wow, did I do that?
She looks like a guy
dressing up like Diana Ross.
So now the loving begins.
Ah!
Come on. Follow my hair.
Aren't these corporations
phony?
You peed in my locker,
didn't you?
So you let them both get away,
the girl
and that delinquent, Trash.
Rockwell wants
his coat back.
I don't think so.
They're both...
under...
- Uh...
-...there.
- Uh, uh, uh...
-Or maybe there.
Uh, right there.
Or somewhere there.
[ Crow giggles ]
Maybe you intend to go down
to convince them
to waste themselves
with some dynamite?
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, I don't think so.
[ Crow chuckles ]
You guys didn't rehearse,
did you?
[ Tom and Mike chuckling ]
That is before
the truth comes out.
A layman wouldn't understand.
Nobody knows they're there.
It's easy to make people
who don't officially exist
...disappear.
The speakerphone is right.
Can you?
Ever love me?
Yes.
Only we've got to catch them
by surprise.
If we let them get away,
it's gonna be very tough.
Uh.
The place is full of tunnels...
I'm just blue-skying here,
but...
...passageways, sewers.
Mm-hm.
It's like a--
- A thing that does some--
-...it's like a jungle.
Without trees or humidity
or tigers.
It's really
a wonderful place.
Who are you?
Hey, get ready
for a lotta laughin'.
-Oh, yeah, the reporter girl.
- Ah. Toblerone.
I hear all about that
on the radio.
You know you're
really something?
[ Tom singing ]
♪ You got me
so I can't sleep at night.
You got a stink.
I was born here
in the Bronx.
[ Excited chatter ]
Hey!
That's why I get
so worked up about it.
Shh!
The show
is about to begin.
Things are looking bad.
I'll say.
If you don't do something
down here
to protect yourselves,
you'll be in trouble.
[ Laughing ]
You hear that, boys?
We are in trouble!
We're getting a big slab
of Toblerone here.
Um, jes?
Hey, cut the crap.
What about you?
And your plans to stay
out in the open?
You think you can stop them?
Huh?
[ All giggling ]
Listen, Thief of Baghdad,
you really think you guys
are safe down here?
Baby, they will never
come down here.
They know very well
we'll bust their asses
if they do.
Dablone!
I want to be called
Da Blonde!
Part the ways.
Part the ways, come on.
Come on, gimme some
laughin' room here.
What is it, honey?
I found this in the tunnel,
under the old schoolhouse.
This disinfestor was
pokin' his nose around.
Suddenly, I feel sad.
I did right, didn't I?
I'm not laughing
very much today.
What's in those guys?
The first time they came here.
They never did before.
They wanna rebuild the Bronx.
You think they'd go ahead
with you jerks down here?
Listen to her, Dablone.
She's got a point.
-Ratwoman is right.
-Right.
Nobody will sit on a john
...full of dynamite.
I did it once,
and it was a mistake.
Skyboy 5,
I repeat the message.
Check for hidden entrance
under slaughterhouse.
Hidden entrance
-I'm Cherokee Jack.
-Corner, 23A and 51A.
I'm tired, and my feet hurt,
and it's hot.
...23A and 51A.
It's the annual paper drive
in the Bronx.
Also, under
the stadium locker rooms,
northside, the same sector.
Ah, it's hard bein' a Nazi,
I shoulda just been a pirate.
I love opening night,
don't you?
[ Mike singing ]
You turn me right round baby,
right round.
And then let them come.
We'll be ready.
God, I love show business.
Juana, what are you doing here?
Go back outside
and keep your eyes open,
understand?
Right. Okay, boys, 10 minutes.
Hurry up!
We're the good Nazis,
aren't we?
[ Tom chuckling ]
Hey, Chuck, put those--
Hot dog! Get your
Hebrew National franks here!
You're not gonna settle anything
with shooting and killing.
I've tried to make Trash here
realize that too.
Have a big bowl of coffee
for breakfast.
What are we supposed to do?
Tell them, come in?
Make yourself at home?
Huh?
No.
[ Crow giggling ]
To lick them, you gotta force
the GC corporation--
I don't wanna lick them.
--to negotiate.
Ah. Hey, put those ramps
over one side.
There's only one way.
Nosferatu!
[ Snarls ]
Kidnap their president.
I do not feel like laughing.
What's wrong with me?
Kidnap the president?
[ Evil giggle ]
Me gusta. I like it!
But, uh--
[ Chuckles ]
Anyway, that's how
we got the guy
outta the cheese cutter.
Hey, gimme a cold one there,
will ya, Sportaroono?
Okay.
[ Crow laughs ]
Yeah.
Ah, it was the most
disgusting thing
I've ever seen.
He was, uh,
wearing his coveralls
so he nothing
but a bag of blood.
Hey, you got that bullet
coming there?
I don't think we have
any bullets.
Come on, come on,
hook me a brewski there.
Mike, oh--
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
They re-showed
the Theismann injury.
I got it on tape.
I got a four-head VCR
so we can freeze it.
It's great.
All right, come on.
Crack me one.
Ah, open a window.
Sure.
No, where's
my 12-ounce curl here, buddy?
Uh, we didn't bring any curls.
I think--
Hey, are you comin' over
for the game?
I got it in surround sound,
it's gonna be great.
Come on, a piston.
I wanna be a mountain man.
Well, that would be
a nice thing to be.
There's more
creamed spinach there, pal.
You're not done.
Come on, eat up. Eat up.
We got more steaks, too.
Crow. Crow.
Hey, come on.
It's Miller time.
Oh, really? I didn't realize
it had gotten so--
No, no, no, no.
Come on, I got
a dead soldier here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That must be terribly tragic
for you. I--
Could you snag me one?
Snag?
[ Snorts ]
No, stop that.
Now, come on, pop me one.
Okay. I'll have
to come around to do it.
Ah, God. I love men's night.
This is great.
[ Alarm sounds ]
Oh, we got movie sign! Come on!
Follow me! Come on!
Ah!
How could anybody
trust a girl
without, uh, being dead?
Mmm, dinosaur pasta.
Num. Num.
They'll all be against us.
Them.
The police...
and maybe the national guard.
Is there any milk?
You're talking about up above.
What if somebody
crawled all the way
underneath the city?
There are people
who have done it,
aren't there?
[ Hissing snarl ]
The robbery...
of the First National Bank.
Then there was the time
they cleaned out Tiffany's.
They had, uh,
that crazy Strike person.
[ Crow snarls ]
Right. Is he around anymore?
Oh, he's around all right,
but, uh,
he would change his hole
for a villa on Long Island.
Is he hard to find?
No. But the hard thing
is to find him in a good mood.
Why?
What if he's in a bad mood?
Then... you got a problem.
A big problem.
[ Tom laughs maniacally ]
Oh, sorry.
Oh, I get it.
This is a metaphor.
For something.
[ Sighs ]
My coffin
is right over here.
[ Snarls ]
Radon levels
are really high down here.
Hello?
Thrust Industries.
Yes, of course, sir.
I don't know,
loden, I guess.
There's nothing in the papers
this morning.
Yes, with the Gore-Tex,
right.
Okay, Al.
Yeah,
the extra-large is fine.
I'll go there myself
and see what I can do.
Will there be
a bra-fitter on duty?
Don't mention it, Al.
It's my pleasure.
Yeah, I'll-- I'll pass
the catalog on to a friend.
Okay.
Uh-huh.
Bye, Al.
What a mess.
He wants the hospital finished
before the elections.
Well, at least
we have his promise
that he'll see Washington
doesn't
interfere in our Bronx business.
Here's my report card.
You have to sign it.
Yeah.
But this damn hospital
is costing us.
All of 80 million dollars.
I don't know who's worse,
the politicians or the gangs.
Or the Ratwoman.
Ugh.
[ Gasps ]
Lupita, no.
Overload,
overload.
Listen, I like your style but,
uh, go easy with
that thing, huh?
I gotta see Strike.
-Go back home.
- Strike.
I gotta see Strike!
We did that line.
Only if he say okay.
I hear when Strike comes in,
the movie really picks up.
Watch out for the wire.
[ Crow singing ]
♪ She's so popul ar
Boo! Boo!
Ah, your magic
isn't very good, kid.
Ah, it always makes
for great cinema
when the caretaker
shows an apartment.
[ Crow singing ]
♪ Popula r.
[ Mike singing ]
♪ How can you have any me at
if you don't eat your pudding
So what do you think?
Gas and electric are included.
Put down a small deposit.
[ Tom singing ]
♪ ...dark sarcasm ,
in the classroom .
Hey--
Thing? Put the luger down.
Strike?
Strike? Are you kidding?
It was way outside.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Mike chuckles ]
Oh, that's a great confession.
You certainly must have heard
I'm crazy, right?
Sure did.
[ Crow mimics Jerry Lewis ]
Joy did lady oh.
They said you're the craziest--
[ Tom mimics Jerry Lewis ]
Oh g'no.
--but you're also the greatest.
[ Tom mimics Jerry Lewis ]
Die, uh, Mister Person
in-the-thing ever.
We need you
to kidnap the president.
Of the United States?
No. The GC Corporation.
Sure, I heard.
You really think I didn't know?
They're especially out
to get you.
I must have this scarf.
It's so kicky.
Oh, watch out!
Her other jaw's
gonna shoot out.
This is so red hot. Ugh.
[ Gasps ]
And rightly so.
How else could
they have succeeded
with the robbery of the century
without you?
Can I get you
a glass of blood?
The National Bank job?
And what about Tiffany's?
She looks
like if Gilda Radner
and Satan had had a baby.
How 'bout the time we--
[ Indistinct ]
Well, there are probably
experimental mind-altering drugs
that'll make me
want to kiss her,
but I don't...
Hey, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
What's in it for me?
That's simple.
If they want
their president back,
they have to put things back
the way they were.
No, doesn't affect me
at all.
Bronx'll be back in the hands
of the gangs.
Which means you'll go back
to being the number one guy
for all the big robberies.
Well, that's sweet, Trash.
Instead of hiding out down here.
You got a point there.
Duh, Trash?
Trash? Hello?
Okay. You can count on me.
I must have blood.
Get ready, Junior.
We're going on a job.
School waits another year.
Fine.
What do you plan
to do with the kid?
Ah, I wouldn't think
of doing a job without him.
Well, well, yeah, but,
wha--? Uh... oh.
It's okay by me, honey,
if you really wanna bring this,
uh--
this useless slob along.
So the hero of our movie
has to go hire another hero.
[ Groans ]
Don't try it again. I'm a pro.
Sure had me fooled.
Shrive me, fool. Hm.
Meanwhile,
in Schaumburg, Illinois.
It's Friday afternoon,
the employees of Citicorp turn
the speakers out of the windows.
[ Tom chuckling ]
Wilford Brimley is 007.
Oh, sorry, sir.
I was rockin' out in here.
Driver, take me down
to the mailbox.
Ah, she's looking for a place
to hang upside down
for the night.
[ Tom chuckling ]
[ Crow hisses ]
Now listen,
it's gonna get much rougher
from here on in,
so be on your guard.
There are more ways
to die down here
than there are
in a Bruce Lee film.
What are some of his films?
Each one is on his own.
If anybody gets hurt
or has to stay behind
for any reason,
don't count on help.
[ Crow hisses ]
I'm setting the thing, Plump.
You know, he looks
like Persis Khambatta.
Bam.
Another hard-hitting look
at cities with buildings.
Who is the boy?
He's yours, remember?
Believe it or not,
he's my son.
And you keep him
buried down here?
Why?
Is up there better?
[ Mike chuckles ]
Yeah. Looks great, actually.
Mm-hm.
Traffic's pretty moderate.
Oh, hey, we got a great,
uh, waterfront park here.
We've been waiting an hour.
Why don't we just go?
And now another look
at Love, American Style.
[ Tom chuckles ]
Neat.
How did he do that with, uh,
package of thing?
And now
the hero subcontractor
has to subcontract to his kid.
I'm doing
the traffic report!
No. I am.
Boy, I miss Toblerone.
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
Moon, let's leave your bag
over there.
- Moon?
- Is his name Moon W. Trash?
Junior, place your charges
about 10 feet apart.
Yeah, right.
I'll take care of this.
You go ahead
and suck face with Vampira.
I just really,
really miss Toblerone.
Hey. Hey, me too.
Uh--
Ah, what was I gonna say?
Damn. Um--
We're going out now.
I've explained everything.
You know what to do.
Yes. Okay.
Good luck.
It's a weird
Cour tship of E d die's Father
episo de here.
Jim Henson's
Chairman Mao Babies.
[ Tom chuckling ]
I'll catch up
on my Marxist dogma
while they're up there.
Comin' in low
out of the rising sun,
scares the hell
out of the executives.
Something about, uh--
'Cause you mentioned bank lines
and, uh-- God.
Well, hey.
It is better up here.
A lot better.
Well, are you coming?
What are you doing? Gee.
Hey, uh, Skipper,
look at the terrorists
over there.
On sale, Seabro barges.
Own a genuine Seabro barge.
[ Tom chuckling ]
Seabro Barge Company.
South access blockaded--
Uh, anyone seen
Lieutenant Kojak?
Tall, bald, ugly.
Anyone?
I got 46 men
covering every--
Uh, we're looking
for Petrocelli over here.
Uh, we're just waitin'
for Banacek to show.
I think they all carpooled.
Hey, they gonna bring
that lunch wagon over here
or are we gonna have
to go over there?
[ All humming the theme
from The Great Escape ]
They blocked all the roads
leading to the island.
How do we get in?
Trash makes a contribution.
We're in already.
Oh, yeah.
[ Goofy laugh ]
Come on.
Huh?
I'm gonna go across town
to this great bar I know.
[ Overlapping chatter ]
Hey, what is this, a hen party?
Shape up.
Come on, you're not on vacation.
Follow me. We got a job to do.
I'll tell ya
about this bar I know later
with all the broads
and all the, uh... Yeah.
The lunch wagon's
on its way.
- All right.
- All right, yeah.
Oh, I gotta tell ya about
this lunch I had one time.
There were broads
and lunch and broads.
Uh, guys?
I sweated all over the Gorp.
Sorry.
This is driving me crazy.
I can't remember
what I was gonna say.
Again the movie states
unflinchingly
that there is a city.
Let's see,
Toblerone recommended
the Guggenheim. Maybe we--
Where the heck
did the city go?
[ Tom chuckling ]
I'm glad we got
those noise cancellation shoes.
You know, I am the undead.
I shouldn't be out in the sun.
Ladies and gentlemen,
here we are on East Island
with a beautiful view
of the Manhattan skyline.
But the official ceremony
for the commencement
of the demolition
of the old historic
gothic castle is about to begin.
In its place will be
the new children's hospital.
And Weekl y Reader News
is o n the scene.
I'll get back to my report
in a minute,
but I just love helicopters.
Trash just seems lost.
The Promise Keepers
are there.
There's a bunch
of white guys down there, sir.
Is that them?
Do that thing.
Hands in pockets,
look up.
And now
we simply kidnap him.
Gotta say, I expected more
of a turnout
for the destruction
of ye olde gothic castle.
The helicopter has just landed
and Mr. Henry G. Clark
is getting off.
Ready to greet him
is New York state governor,
Malcolm Biddle.
Don't laugh at his name.
He gets mad at that.
I bet this live coverage
is really pulling
in the numbers.
Mm-hm.
Folks,
I now you're all excited
about the
munitions plant going--
I--I mean
the children's hospital.
Hello, Mr. Clark.
How was your trip?
Very good, thank you.
Ah. Please come with me.
Would you like a pop?
We have some photographers
waiting here.
They're gonna
be snapping some pictures.
And some bras.
We want New Yorkers
to know who the man is
who's building their future city
for them.
I guess a little notoriety
never hurt anyone.
Where's the buffet?
We may have
some questions as well
if you don't mind.
No, no. Not at all.
As you have read in the papers,
Mr. Clark,
president and main stockholder
of General
Construction Corporation
has not only donated
the entire island to the state
but generously agreed
to do the complete razing job
free of charge.
Shh. Shh.
These mule deer
are extremely wary.
Delta One, Delta One.
Yeah.
Radio links established.
-Okay. Right.
- Situation?
Everything here
is under control.
-This is good gum.
- Unde rstood.
This is a message
to unit leaders.
Message to unit leaders.
Until the ceremony is over
all river craft,
including ferries,
are to be kept clear
of the island.
Hey, that's not fair.
Now report
your situations.
- Lot of them.
-Hi.
Sigma Two, over?
Area one is covered.
Roger, Sigma Two.
Omega Six, come in please.
Omega Six.
Should we spread out
or something?
Roger. Able Three?
Able Three here. Over.
Able Three.
[ Mocking overlapping babble ]
Move on to area five.
That's all right,
I'll catch you later.
Wow.
And on behalf
of the General Construction
Corporation--
Mm-hm?
I have the great honor
of asking Governor Biddle--
Not piddle.
--to give the first blow
of the pick.
Thank you very much, Mr. Clark.
I'm very proud.
Don't screw it up, Piddle.
I'll show 'em
who's Piddle.
I'll bring this cathedral down
with a mighty blow
of my hammer.
Uh, ow! Owie!
It hurts my wrist.
The governor's just given
the first symbolic blow
against the wall
of the old building.
Marking the beginning
of the demolition.
The new children's hospital
to be constructed
-by Mr. Clark's company
- "Hospittle."
...will be styled
to blend in with
the Eighth Wonder project
of the future:
the complete rebuilding
of the Bronx
into a fashionable
residential area.
Spench, Punch, you guys.
one of
our campaign promises
and by gum,
we're gonna carry it out.
Starsky and Carole King.
Frank, what are we doing?
Uh-oh. I think we need
a little diversion.
I'll take care of it, Conan.
Why'd you call me Conan?
- Where did you get Conan?
-How?
I know what to do.
[ Crow hisses ]
Go to it.
The Bronx project
is part and parcel of--
A rubbery Jimmy Smits.
[ Crow chuckling ]
Lies! They're all lies!
It's about time
the truth was told!
News!
This is actual news!
Why don't you tell everyone
what's really going on
in the Bronx?
-That nosy crusader again.
-Well, I'll tell ya.
I can tell you
because I've seen it
with my own eyes!
People are being slaughtered
in there.
Exterminated!
[ Crow snarls]
And this...
genocide is being condoned
by our dear governor.
Why don't you admit it,
Governor Biddle?!
Not Piddle.
Why don't you admit
that you're in cahoots
with Clark,
that you're giving
GCC's Clark slush--
Can't you stop her?
Um, stop.
It's an obscene, corrupt--
She's got a gun.
- Hmm?
-She's gonna shoot Mr. Clark.
Killers!
Nice governor.
Murders and criminals!
[ Gunshot ]
Oh, my God!
Murder at some
historic cathedral somewhere.
[ Panicked chatter ]
Get 'em out of here.
Nosferatu
was murdered today.
Now we need
a wooden stake here.
She didn't have a gun.
Nothing.
-All right, motherfucker, move.
-She didn't have a gun.
You're blind, buddy.
I saw it myself.
The rodent kingdom mourned
the loss of the Rat Queen today.
This is just plain crooked.
I hate evil corporations
that try and evacuate the Bronx
and plant guns.
- Yeah.
- Oh! Just burns me.
Colonel Mustard
looks nervous.
Trash stumbles
into the middle of the action.
No!
[ Gunfire ]
Eww.
Wow. Hey, Trash has
got Italian bun-huggers.
Eww.
[ Gunfire ]
There's something sort of
Richard Dreyfuss-inian
about this guy.
[ Crow giggling ]
Exploding boards!
[ Tom whimpers ]
Oh.
Good afternoon,
Mr. Murdering Clark.
Uh, just Mr. Clark is fine.
Come on.
Let's get outta here.
He's being kidnapped
by Kiss.
[ Crow giggling ]
[ Gunfire, groans ]
Todd!
The Battleship Potemkin's
losing a lot of crew.
Just leave a salt lick
for the rabbits and--
Stay down!
Sega!
[ Mike chuckling, gunshot ]
[ Explosion, groans ]
The physics of this
make no sense.
To all emergency units
operating around the Bronx,
President Clark
has been kidnapped.
Repeat, GCC President Clark
[ Gunshot, groans ]
[ Gunshot ]
What's with
the drum sound?
[ Chuckling ]
Ah, they're looking
for Frog One.
[ Tom whispers ]
French Connection.
[ Mike whispers ]
Got it.
And now Pinch
in the silent spot.
I've grown to like Flank.
Strike.
Stripe?
Go on, go on.
With me.
Come on.
There's no sound in here.
[ Explosion ]
[ Screams ]
This trampoline accident
could have been avoided.
Never use a trampoline
with unstable TNT
in your pocket.
Okay.
Maybe this
is an outrageously funny
Italian movie.
I think it
was originally conceived
as a still photograph.
Back when ballet dancers
moonlighted as chauffeurs.
Skyboy 9 to Central.
I may have something. Over.
I think it may be a cold.
Over.
The old historic
gothic castle subway stop.
Gotta get
at the canned peaches.
Go on.
No, please.
I don't have any tokens.
Hey, grandma,
we got another one.
[ Chuckles ]
What do you want from me?
Who are you?
Shut up!
Don't make me think.
I can't multitask.
[ Tom chuckling ]
Squad Number Two
to the sewer system
north of the port.
[ Siren blaring ]
Squad Nine
to the subway tunnels
in Sector Four,
125th Street entrance.
Come on, move it!
All right,
the bobsled team has arrived.
Good.
Move it!
Always last, aren't ya?
Is that the way
to motivate Wade?
Dead as a doornail.
I was in the basement.
Uh, something happen up here?
[ Beeping noise ]
The movie's backing up.
The ones who went after them
are all dead too.
I'm on the phone.
Hello.
Wangler here.
Shift Seven Squad to the Bronx.
And give me an okay.
Operation Stop Flink.
You people never learn.
You've got to hit them first.
Yes, I know, but--
I'm on the phone!
Okay.
Intercept them before they reach
the Bronx.
And don't go
the same way they did.
It's all tore up.
Go around.
They're placing explosives.
I'm on my way to the Bronx
to direct operations myself.
[ Sirens blaring ]
And Squadron Nine
arrives at the Carnegie Deli.
Let's make liquor delivery.
...117.
Squad Eight
to emergency exit 826.
Hurry! Hurry!
We didn't get a permit to film!
Beware
of possible dynamite charges.
That's always good advice.
Mm-hm.
I can't see
where this would continue
-for another 20 minutes.
-Right over there.
The Bronx is leaking.
Hold it.
Is this moisture
gonna frizz my hair out?
Listen, whatever happens,
I'd like to get something--
something straight between us.
-You comin' on to me?
- Just no way.
Dump my used oil
in the gutter.
You really think that I
and I alone
am responsible for all the--
the unpleasant things
that have been going on
in the Bronx?
Hmm?
It's very complicated.
You understand.
The decisions were not all mine.
Yeah, but you're still a wheel.
[ Explosion ]
Whoops. Run!
[ Coughs ]
-So?
-Okay!
Aha! Let's go.
I gotta get you
to kindergarten.
Let's move it.
Maybe this is a chick film,
and we just don't get it.
You know, we haven't taken
the time to enjoy
the death
of that devil vampire woman.
Right.
You ever think, Ernie,
that the filth comin' down
could've been your own?
Eww.
Well, we spotted
some floaters, sir.
Eww!
[ Sobbing ]
Get back!
Get back! Get back!
[ Screams ]
Sir, we're okay.
That's what these suits
are for.
[ Crow screams ]
Panicking commander.
The director had a vision.
Make guys jump
in slow motion.
[ Screams ]
This flameproof suit sucks!
Oh!
Geez. Bring back Toblerone!
-Yeah!
-We want Toblerone!
So these apartments,
the kitchens'll be real open
and airy.
Laundry on every floor.
Wow, this is gonna be
a terrific development.
[ Gunfire, groans ]
We always jump
and forget to shoot.
[ Tom whimpering ]
Guard! Uh, oh wait.
[ Gunshots ]
Shmook? Chunk?
Zip? I'm afraid.
Chunks? Krull?
Fleb? Torq? Ryan?
Oh. Oh.
[ Crow groans ]
Oh, I tore a groin muscle.
Geez, it looks like
Princ e of Persia.
Well, it's nicer than
the Soldier Field bathrooms.
[ Tom chuckling ]
Hey,
the Los Angeles River.
Tonight,
on the Channel Nine News.
Strike!
Yes.
It sounds like
the Banace k suite
for orchestra and guitar.
[ Crow giggling ]
[ Mike mimics drums ]
You too can play
the electric guitar in two days.
[ Tom mimics guitar noises ]
[ Tom and Crow
mimic guitar noises ]
-Don't shoot!
-It's the president!
-It's me, Clark, don't shoot.
- "Hobalone?"
- "Hobalone."
-Am I glad to see you guys.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Groans ]
Get back!
[ Gunshots ]
[ Groans ]
Oh, high-bouncin' bullets.
[ Gunfire ]
Look,
just leave the Bronx.
We're just trying
to do our job. Ow.
[ Tom whimpering ]
Oh?
Hey, it's our one guy.
Blink. Spinch,
is that you?
Hmm?
Are you our one guy?
Can't decide
who I like better.
John-John Rambo.
You try that again,
and you'll look like
a tea-strainer.
A hostage is no good dead.
I've gotta be
worth something,
if you're going through
all that much fuss topside.
Then, you know who to root for,
right?
Torq, I'm surprised at you.
'Cause if we make it,
so do you.
They're coming,
they're coming.
Where are they?
Hang on,
I'll come over there.
Right now down Tunnel Four.
Charger set?
Yeah.
Okay. Let's go.
Come on.
Come on, you heard him.
[ Imitating thick accent ]
Now down Tunnel Four.
Move.
D'oh. I was hoping we'd see
that darling explosion gesture
he makes...
[ Chuckling ]
[ Explosion ]
Really I just need
to lay down for a minute.
-No, no. I'm fine.
-Poor sick dope.
No, I think I'd better--
-Seemed fine in the theater.
-Come on, have a little of this.
Oh, no, I'm feeling better.
No, maybe later.
Hey, what would the Mads
be calling at this hour for?
Okay, it's like this, Nelson.
I've been going over
your Arbitron numbers
and despite our efforts
to boost your ratings
they've been flateroo.
We tried MST Nights,
but the network
just didn't go for it.
Frankly, I blame you guys.
Us? Why?
Why?
Because there's no kid.
Every successful television show
has had a winsome child
of some sort.
Take your, uh, Family Affairs ,
your Full Houses ,
your The Avengers .
The Avengers didn't have
a cute kid.
Well, split hairs if you will,
the point is we need
something cute on the show.
Gentlemen, I give you
Timmy Bobby Rusty.
Huh? Huh?
Timmy Bobby Rusty?
Come on, look.
He's got red hair.
Uncle Forrester,
are you my daddy?
No. Well, Mike?
Adorable, huh?
I can already feel
those ratings goin' boom.
Timmy Bobby, uh, Rusty.
[ Chuckles ]
What does Timmy Bobby Rusty
do exactly?
Do? What does he do?
Why, he's adorable
and people will love it.
[ Doorbell ]
Oh, that must be
the Arbitron numbers.
Hey, lady.
Are you my nana?
Look, Clay, I gotta be honest,
I don't like kids.
Oh, damn!
Timmy Bobby Rusty didn't bring
the ratings up one scintilla.
[ Grunts ]
[ Sobs ]
Well, don't worry, Nelson.
There's still my nude celebrity
trapshoot.
[ Chuckles]
Pull.
[ Chuckles ]
Send a squad, down the manhole!
- "Yonder manhole?"
-Eight didn't get through.
Why waste any more squads?
Who's this
personal injury lawyer
who keeps showing up?
Because we're leading them
into a trap.
They cannot get out of
the Queens sewers
or the Manhattan lines either.
- Fine.
-Fine.
Well, don't get mad.
It's true. Come on.
I'll be in my office
waiting for news,
good or bad.
And get those oven mitts
off your shoulders.
Hello. Yes, it's Wangler.
I wanna win a wangler!
What are those idiots doing,
sleeping?
Oh,
and they are sleeping.
Listen, I want a squad sent
to the east end sewer now!
Sir, we're ready
to go down now.
Hurry it up!
Okay, yo, gotcha.
What's it like?
Go down quickly!
Hmm?
Where are you? Oh.
Oh! That was my sore ear,
Trash.
There against the wall.
You guys'll never make it.
We might. Come on!
If you let me go,
I promise I'll talk--
Shut your damn trap.
We know your promises.
Are you guys gonna
blow us up again?
Now!
Ah.
- Mm-hm.
-There they are! Go, go!
-Hmm?
- And?
- Hmm?
[ Explosion, screams ]
Come on, big shot.
Let's go.
Oh, bummer.
Hope they don't blow
our crotches off.
[ Explosion, groans ]
Oh, what did you step in?
D'oh, d'oh.
Wait, I got it.
It's all twisted.
Oh damn.
Hold it.
Now, I'll be--
You go that way.
I'm just gonna just--
wait for me.
We all gotta get up there!
Wonder if the silver pants guys
hate the blue milkmen guys.
[ Explosion, groans ]
Ow, I shouldn't have wore
these tight Italian underthings.
[ Sighs ]
Why don't you think
we'll make it?
I think we're doing fine.
Hold it.
Geez, they keep spawning.
I am officially hot
in this suit.
[ Tom chuckling ]
Boil-in-bag people.
- Mmm.
-Mmm.
Whoa, where's the ladder?
We're right on top of 'em.
The Fourth Squad is blocking
the main exit.
So we've got 'em trapped.
That's a beautiful haiku.
It's only a matter
of minutes now.
That was a stroke
of genius, sir.
Need a light, sir?
Don't congratulate me
too quickly.
Hmm?
Rimsky-Korsakov's delightful
"Spike Descending,"
written originally
for the ballet.
Whoa, rope burns
on the willy.
[ Mike chuckling ]
I'm getting tingly.
Team building
through Outward Bound.
Good boy.
It's easy.
But you're so big and brave,
Trash.
Hey, this is easy.
And fun!
I'm building my pecs
as I'm evacuating the Bronx.
[ Gunfire, groans ]
My wallet!
[ Tom singing ]
♪ Baby hold on to m e.
Oh, God,
he's snugger than ever.
Alfred Hitchcock's rope.
Not the movie, they just
borrowed his rope.
Go ahead.
That way.
[ Mimicking the soundtrack ]
[ Gunshot ]
Ow. Fine,
here's your stupid rope.
[ Gunfire, groans ]
Wow, he must be
in "God Mode"
with unlimited ammo.
Let's go. Move!
Pa!
[ Explosion, groans ]
He looks like Vanity.
[ Crow giggling ]
New York City ran out
of cops today.
I should've known!
Quick!
Strawberry Quik,
that's what I'm thirsty for.
[ Gunshot, groans ]
Me too! Me too!
I wanna die!
[ Gunshot ]
Thank you.
Shoot 'em all.
We'll make more.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Screams ]
Oh.
Huh?
Why you murdering little rat.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah.
You're going down next,
Dad.
Let's go.
So tell me honestly,
what do you think
of my security force?
[ Explosion ]
We were about to run off
the ledge anyway.
I repeat--
My face is long.
[ Chuckling ]
You've got them.
But if they get into the Bronx
with all those gangs,
I cannot guarantee it.
Would you say Mr. Clark
is in danger?
Absolutely.
Man f rom U.N.C.L.E.
swis h pan.
Ooh.
There's a risk
that they will kill him.
Hello?
I will talk with you later.
Ah.
Methadone.
[ Spits ]
Eight O'Clock Coffee!
No sugar, you idiot!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
No sugar. It makes me crazy!
Crazy!
[ Tom chuckling ]
And why do you wanna be
a scale model here at ConglomCo?
Vroom, vroom.
[ Evil chuckling ]
Hmm? What?
You like that, huh?
You like it when
I touch your penthouse?
Yeah, yeah.
You don't like me, do you?
You think you're better than me.
I'm getting all
of your names.
You, your name? And you?
Uh-huh, we got yours and--
Ha! You?
[ Tom chuckling ]
All right,
same time tomorrow then?
Okay. Thank you
for your time.
Don't look at me
as I walk away. I'm leaving.
Bye.
Ah, what a jerk that guy is.
Hey, condo, you like that guy?
Nah.
I am an architect
at a small Midwestern Bronx.
The first building
was Neo-Roman in style and--
[ Softly ]
More later.
Miss Gibbs?
I'm not here.
Take down a press communique.
No.
Our president--
Uh-huh.
Mr. Clark
Yeah, great.
I'll take care of that.
has been kidnapped by a
a group of Bronx criminals.
Good.
Their demands are absurd.
They want croppies nailed
to every lamppost.
Huh?
Ten million dollars
That's absurd.
or they'll kill him
in cold blood.
Yes.
These are not people fighting
for their homes,
-Um, you
-but crooks--
you got a
--hungering after money
and blood.
- Okay, just- it's just--
-Especially blood.
Can't see.
Because the time they give us
to collect this enormous sum--
Mm-hm?
--is ridiculous.
It's none time.
Which they know perfectly well.
Thank you, wise wall.
They're right on top of us.
That tunnel there.
Okay.
You gotta take me
to the potty. I have to go.
Wait there.
Boy, if you're into
creeping around corners,
this is your movie.
Hmm.
A herd of ibexes!
Maybe not.
Ah! This is from
the Hard to Find Tools catalog.
Ah.
Thank you, Brookstone.
I knew this would come in handy.
Whoop!
[ Gunfire, groans ]
[ Gunshot, groans ]
Man. Buck F ever has
a real problem
with these silver guys.
Real hard to find
genuine Ringo caps anymore.
Go on.
Fourth Squad went off
on the wrong track, sir.
They fell into
some kind of trap.
But the Fifth Squad
has 'em cornered
-near the main floor section.
- Stepping off the LEM.
That's one small step
for man.
This is the end of the line.
If we let them get away
from us this time,
there will not
be a second chance.
Is--? Is that okay?
You--? Are you there?
Of course, the president.
Put your mother on!
It was his life that
I was talking about.
Okay!
Check all the buildings
on the right.
A completely new outdoor
walking scene.
Stevie Nicks!
Form in with me. Come on.
Caw! Caw!
[ Tom chuckling ]
Gotta bring eggshells
to school tomorrow, Dad.
So this is the basement
of the Bronx, huh?
You guys have any problem
with seepage down here?
Hey, they made it!
Here they come!
Get him!
[ Angry shouting ]
Hit it, girls!
Get him! Get him!
Mister Sinatra
coming through.
My people love me.
They love
my housing developments.
Thank you.
Get Richard Dreyfuss.
Get him!
[ Angry shouting continues ]
If ever a scene cried out
for Toblerone--
What are they gonna do?
Tapdance him to death?
[ Tom chuckling ]
That's enough! Leave him alone!
[ Gunshot ]
No, wait. This could be it.
Yes! Yes! There he is!
Yes, there his is.
[ Laughs ]
Yay! Whoo!
Tobey!
Come on out.
Just drink him in.
Stand back!
Oh, do it.
Yes.
I'm warning you,
you'll answer for this,
before a court of law.
[ Tom with a heavy accent ]
Ju cahn handle da truth.
Sure, sure.
Well, guys, you did it.
Nice going, Trash.
Congratulations.
Splink.
Aren't those earrings
a bit dressy?
Now, let me see
what a president looks like.
-He got two arms!
- Two hearts?
Two legs!
He just like us!
[ Dablone and crowd laughs ]
We have Toblerone laugh.
Yes.
I admit I don't get it.
So here the mother...
finally is.
Oh! Ah!
I'd like to kill him!
[ Through clenched jaw ]
Uh, this hurts. Mr--
-I'd like to cut his throat!
- Mr. Toblerone.
But if I do,
we can't negotiate.
And now!
I'm so lucky
to study with him.
They will listen to us!
If they want their
president back.
[ Dablone and crowd laughs ]
Frankly,
I'm not into Toblerone.
Dablone, Dablone!
The disinfestors,
they're outside,
preparing an all-out attack!
[ Gasps ]
Richard Carpenter's
The Fo g.
Gas! Gas!
GATT? GATT?
There's a trade treaty here?
Get out!
Let's get out!
[ Pan icked chatter ]
Huggy Bear. Michael Jackson.
Micky Dolenz.
Randy Quaid. Bob Dylan.
Uh, Huggy Bear again.
Don't panic!
-It's gas!
-Go on!
Somebody grab
the coffee!
Get the horses
outta the barn!
Come on, people.
We're circus.
We're bigger than this.
Hey! Over here!
Help me move
my record albums.
Oh man, those
Annie Sprinkle performances.
[ Mike and Tom retching ]
[ Woman crying ]
Quick,
get to the halls of medicine.
[ Coughing, groaning ]
[ Gunfire ]
Rat a tat tat.
Come on. Come on.
Please, please me.
Look, it says
"Arne Saknussemm."
Hey, Jimmy's ditching.
[ Gunfire ]
- Huh?
- Oh.
[ Explosion ]
Uh, it's not worth
bending down for. Come on.
We have downpayment
assistance
if that's a problem.
[ Gunfire ]
D'oh, they shot
the asthmatic Nazi.
[ Gunfire, groans ]
Okay...
I did something like this
in a management seminar once.
The Monopoly guy
has escaped.
[ Crow growls ]
Boards bad.
[ Growls ]
[ Tom coughs ]
I get my puffer?
[ Coughs ]
Is this the end for Bilge?
Trash.
Hey, someone
put the Trash out.
[ Chuckles ]
Rats! Get the rats off me!
[ Grunts ]
Hey, Fudge is buff.
[ Tom whimpering, sobbing ]
[ Chuckling ]
[ Explosion ]
Wow, the Bronx
[ Siren wails]
has never been
so densely populated.
Apparently some of you
do not want to leave the Bronx.
As a first step,
we urge you to try thinking
outside the Bronx.
D'oh.
Hi. Kill us.
[ Gunfire ]
Thank you!
[ Tom chuckling ]
You guys, you know,
I normally like a movie
with silver guys jumping out
of trucks but I gotta say
I'm a bit, uh,
disappointed with this one.
Yeah.
Okay. But hurry,
and wash up.
[ Gunfire ]
Wangler, where are you?
It's me! Clark!
Get my limo!
[ Gunfire ]
So anyway, I was saying.
Wangler!
Wangler, it's me! Clark!
If you want, uh, Wangler,
I see Mr. Clark, sir.
Where?
Right here.
He just came out
of East Sixth exit.
I'll take care of it.
Personally.
How?
Three minutes.
And leave it in the shell.
Don't worry.
Our way.
I wish he knew
I liked him like this.
[ Sighs ]
Geez, Pork's little panties
have to be jammed way up there
by this time.
[ Groans ]
I'm not subletting,
damn it.
[ Crow giggling ]
[ Gunfire ]
These guys are dumber
than invertebrates.
[ Gunfire ]
It's Old West days
in the Bronx.
[ Gunshot ]
Get outta there.
That's the good china.
All I can say is, I'm...
very, very happy to see you.
Me too, sir.
Ah, they're in love.
Well, now...
Is there a bug
on my shoulder?
[ Tom chuckling ]
[ Gunshot, groans ]
He died as he died.
Dead.
[ Humming along
with exciting music ]
[ Gunshot, groans ]
Geez, everybody dressed like
Randle P. McMurphy
to leave the Bronx.
[ Gunfire, groans ]
Oh, really bad time
to do your storm windows.
Okay, just gonna
climb up my window
and change my storm ladders.
Panty raid!
Man on the floor.
[ Sirens blaring ]
[ Tom singing]
Motion in the ocean,
his air hose broke.
Lots of bubbles,
lots of trouble.
[ Chuckles ]
You know, as destroyed
as the Bronx is,
there's still a Kinkos
on every corner.
[ Mike singing to the score ]
Leave the Bronx,
leave the Bronx, the Bronx,
leave the Bronx.
Oh, hey, look.
A perfectly good can
of cream corn.
Nope.
[ Gunfire ]
Disinfestation is just
beyond these clowns.
[ Crow giggling, Groans ]
All right, we're here
in the KROQ supervan
giving out--
[ Screams ]
Hey, rats.
That was my van!
Lindsey Buckingham, P.I.
Well, that's taken care of.
Did you bring me anything?
Soon the rest will be over too.
And then
you'll say goodbye.
[ Groaning ]
Uh, not so hard.
See you later, Mr. Wangler.
See you, Mr. President.
When do I get a key
to the bathroom?
Uh, you can let go now.
Henry Silva,
for all your Silva needs.
Uh, now he's mad.
Racquetball at seven,
Mr. Wangler.
Wait, his Targa
turned into a van.
I just disinfestated
the Bronx.
I'm going to Disneyland!
[ Chuckling ]
[ Gunshot, groans ]
That one was just for fun.
Sorry, my horn is out
so I'm just shooting.
[ Gunshot ]
Oh, Trunk has been hit
in the hunky shoulder.
Ah, finally
the ultimate showdown
between vaguely evil
and somewhat ambiguous.
[ Gunshots ]
Ooh.
Oh, geez.
[ Explosion ]
He made one mistake.
-He parked.
- Yep.
Maybe next time
you'll yield the right of way.
[ Tom chuckling ]
He looks like
a cross between
a silverback gorilla
and Eddie Van Halen.
I wonder what
burning Henry Silva smells like.
Maybe I could salvage
those wheel covers,
then I could get a van.
I could have
a real max party van!
Woo hoo!
I see. Now the movie
has bookended itself
what with the explosion
at the beginning
and now this at the end
and all the explosions
within the middle part.
I don't know.
Maybe I will leave the Bronx.
[ Mike singing ]
Go ahead
and hate your neighbor.
Go ahead and cheat a friend.
Okay, Omega Man,
you can move your stuff in now.
Hi, Chunk.
Hey, Flink.
Uh, you're wondering
how I keep my hair
so full, aren't ya?
[ Tom chuckling ]
No?
No dialogue whatsoever?
Okay.
Pa!
[ Mike mimicking a crow ]
Pa! Pa!
Let's go back down.
I don't like it here up top.
[ Tom chuckles ]
Sorry, my prepubescently
androgynous offspring.
[ Tom chuckles ]
[ Tom whistles theme
from The Andy Griffith Show ]
Trash.
It's Moon.
Come with us.
Everyone call me Trash
so I can see
where you could get the idea
my name is Trash.
Pa!
Uh-huh. Yeah. Sure.
Whatever. Goodbye.
Hope you rot in preschool, kid.
Wow.
Well, this just nipped
my habit of watching movies
with silver guys jumping out
of trucks right in the bud.
- Clean up in Borough Five.
- Ooh!
Hey, this gives me an idea.
I'll be right back.
[ Mike hums along to end music ]
Crow?
Of course, there was
a Coppola in it.
[ Mike continues humming along
to end music ]
Pretty nice grouping
of corpses they got going there.
Yep, yep, yep.
You know,
wish I wasn't here right now.
-Hey.
- Ow.
[ Tom singing ]
♪ Leave the Bro nx
♪ Leave Bronx
Leave Bronx
♪ Leave Bronx, huh!
I think I get the idea.
Ow!
[ Tom singing ]
♪ Leave Bronx. Boogi e!
- ♪ Le ave Bronx
- All right.
♪ Leave Bronx, b aby,
leave Bronx
- Ow. Ow.
- ♪ Ah, lea ve Bro nx
-♪ Ah, leave Bronx!
- Okay, that's good.
- ♪ L eave Bronx
-Ow, it hurts!
- Watch that thing, okay?
- ♪ Leave B ro nx
- ♪ T hen leave Bronx
-Would you stop that?
♪ Why don't you leave Bron x?
I think we get the--
Stop it!
[ Tom singing ]
♪ I said, leave Bron x.
♪ Baby, leave Bronx.
♪ Come on, leave Bronx.
- Okay.
-♪ Ow, le ave B ronx.
[ Crow hums ]
♪ When I say leave Bron x.
[ Crow continues humming ]
♪ Leave Bron x.
Stop it.
[ Tom singing ]
♪ Leave Bronx . Stop it.
- Ow!
- ♪ Leave B ron x.
[ Crow continues humming ]
♪ Baby, leave Bronx .
[ Tom holds a note ]
♪ La na na na na
[ Tom singing "Separate Ways" ]
♪ Someday love will find y ou
♪ Break those chains
that bind you
- ♪ On e night will remind you
- Ow! Ow.
Get that guitar--
♪ How we left and went our
se p arate wa ys
Okay. Okay, all right.
That's good. That's good.
[ Tom holding a note ]
That's good.
[ Crow and Tom giggling ]
Thank you. Thank you.
- Uh-huh.
- Separate Ways.
That's great.
You did a great job.
- Thank you.
-You liked that lick?
This is Dolby Stereo
reminding you
to leave the Bronx.
[ Tom chuckles ]
[ Crow singing]
New tasting, improv--
Hey, where's Tomalicious?
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe he was ordered
to leave the Bronx.
[ Laughs ]
That's not funny.
I'm sorry.
Can we read a letter?
-Yeah, let's read a letter.
-Okay.
[ Helicopter noise ]
Well, I got a nice letter here
-from, uh, Ben Hurt in--
- All right, right here.
Keep it steady there, baby.
- Right. Yeah.
-What the...?
Easy, easy, easy.
Ah.
[ Laughs ]
Hi, Tom.
Hi there.
Hey, where'd you
get the helicopter?
Ah, it's just a rental.
It's not mine.
Well, who's flying it?
I don't know.
Some guy, works for the company.
Rick, I think.
Oh, okay. Well, can we read
this letter here?
Yeah. Better hurry,
'cause I'm on the clock here.
All right. Okay.
-Yeah.
-It's from, uh, Ben Hurt.
-Ben Hur?
-He's got some, uh-
-Ben Hurt.
-Ah, thank you.
Ben Hurt and he's
got some nice pictures here.
Put that on still store,
Cambot.
-Ah, very nice.
- Lovely.
Look at Crow.
Help me, I'm Crow.
Nice renditions.
[ Crow and Mike chuckling ]
Anyway, he says, uh,
"I'm your biggest fan
and I've seen all your shows
and I have to say each one
is the funniest thing
I've ever seen."
Ah, progressive enjoyment.
Uh, okay. Whatever.
"You guys are so funny.
I just have one question.
Where do Crow, Tom Servo,
and Gypsy sleep?"
-Wherever the hell we want!
-Yeah!
[ Laughs ]
Anyway, thanks a lot, Ben.
That's a great letter.
Okay. Bring me up, Rick.
-Buh-bye, fellas.
-Okay, buh-bye, then.
- Woo!
-Bu h-bye!
-Bye!
Odd little guy, huh?
Yeah.
[ Laughing in the distance ]
Clayton!
Clayton, what is
that infernal noise?
Clayton?
I'm eating cereal, Mother.
[ Laughter continues ]
Clayton, that noise.
Make it stop.
Oh, all right,
you crazy old loon.
Hey! Keep it down!
I got my mother in the
home over here.
Hey.
You no like my laughing, eh?
Eh?
[ Continues laughing ]
If you could just keep it down
just a little bit.
[ Laughter slows and stops ]
Hey, what you in there for?
I hear of a jack in the box
but I never hear
of a lady in the box!
[ Laughs ]
Oh. Ha. It's really
a personal matter.
-You shut up.
-Yes. Shutting up.
And you, you come with me,
you beautiful lady.
[ Laughs ]
Eat my dust, Clayton.
I'm going off with
this beautiful,
olive-skinned man.
Well, drive safely.
[ Chuckles, sighs ]
It's been an odd day.
[ Spits ]
[ Laughs ]